import { Category } from 'src/app/interfaces/category.interface';

export default {
  name: 'Урок от 3го марта',
  cards: [{
    question: 'adversity',
    answer: 'невзгоды',
  }, {
    question: 'obstacles',
    answer: 'препятствия',
  }, {
    question: 'embarking',
    answer: 'начинать',
  }, {
    question: 'tripping',
    answer: 'спотыкаться',
  }, {
    question: 'devastating',
    answer: 'ошеломляющей/разрушительный/ужасающий',
  }, {
    question: 'avoid',
    answer: 'избегать',
  }, {
    question: 'disease',
    answer: 'болезнь',
  }, {
    question: 'slurred',
    answer: 'невнятный',
  }, {
    question: 'dwell on',
    answer: 'останавливаться',
  }, {
    question: 'remain',
    answer: 'оставаться',
  }, {
    question: 'significant',
    answer: 'значительный',
  }, {
    question: 'instantly',
    answer: 'мгновенно',
  }, {
    question: 'inauspicious',
    answer: 'непопулярной',
  }, {
    question: 'emerged',
    answer: 'возникали',
  }, {
    question: 'accurate',
    answer: 'точный',
  }, {
    question: 'to attend',
    answer: 'посещал',
  }],
} as Category;
